outdoorhub.com 2016-11-24

# Our official Privacy Page and Notice of OutdoorHub | OutdoorHub

_Effective January 17, 2012._

Outdoor Hub is the operator of www.outdoorhub.com. As part of its business, Outdoor Hub, LLC gathers personally identifiable information on its websites as well as anonymous data regarding the website and your activities on the site. Outdoor Hub, LLC takes its privacy obligations very seriously.

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com).

## What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information (name, email address and mailing address) you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis (for example in your forums profile) and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site

Whenever Outdoor Hub, LLC collects personally identifiable about you, it reserves the right to use that information for marketing Outdoor Hub, LLC and its various activities. This is true in both the unpaid and paid sections of the Outdoor Hub, LLC sites. Outdoor Hub, LLC shall use the personally identifiable data collected to undertake a variety of marketing activities including, but not limited to, email, direct mail, site personalization, telephone marketing and other digital and traditional methods of advertising and communication. Outdoor Hub, LLC does not sell or “monetize” data to 3rd parties. Outdoor Hub, LLC, however, does and will send marketing messages on behalf of its sponsors and partners. It will do so without giving any of your personally identifiable information to those sponsors and partners for their own use.

## Personal Information You Choose to Provide

### Registration Information

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register to be a member of www.outdoorhub.com register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts. You may also provide additional comments on how you see www.outdoorhub.com servicing your needs and interests.

### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

### Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers, and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

## How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com).

From time to time, Outdoor Hub, LLC will allow its Sponsors or marketing partners to offer Outdoor Hub, LLC site visitors an opportunity to “opt-in” to receive marketing information directly from that Sponsor or marketing partner. In such cases, on the registration page, an “opt-in” question will appear clearly explaining that by checking the box you agree to share your personally identifiable information with that particular Sponsor or marketing partner. If there is not a Sponsor “opt-in” question on a registration form, Outdoor Hub, LLC will not give any of the data collected to any Sponsor or partner.

## Tell-A-Friend/Share This

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend [email a friend, refer a friend, send to a friend, email a page, invite a friend] about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Outdoor Hub, LLC stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

## What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies.

## How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

As you use our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. For example, some of our partners operate stores or provide services on our site, while others power offerings developed by us for your use. We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

## Widgets

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

## Facebook Connect

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## Notice of New Services and Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com).

## How Do We Protect Your Information?

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com).

## How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com).

## Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [customerservice@outdoorhub.com](mailto:customerservice@outdoorhub.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

## Certain Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

## What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

## Material Changes to Policy

Outdoor Hub, LLC may make material changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you should periodically visit this page to view the current Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change to this Privacy Policy, Outdoor Hub, LLC shall send an email advising of the change to all whose email addresses we have collected and retained pursuant to the terms set forth above.

Outdoor Hub, LLC  
c/o Outdoor Hub, LLC  
30800 Telegraph Road, Ste 4805  
Bingham Farms, MI 48025
